Prophecy Time
Come on, come here!
You pose as a pastor. Are you really a pastor?
Yes, sir!
Because I'm seeing you acting and
doing the work of a pastor.
Yes, sir!
Are you a pastor?
But if you are a pastor, what
is your business with rituals?
I needed money.
You went there to do what?
To take money.
He is my husband, Man of God, please deliver him!
Man of God, please deliver him.
He is a pastor.
He used to do the work of God.
Come out.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Testimony Time
My name is Pastor Stephen Zoryiku.
I'm a first year marketing student at Accra Polytechnic.
This is my wife Evelyn and
we are from Ghana.
On Monday Prophet gave
me a prophecy
that he saw me as a pastor and I said "yes" and that what is my
connection with the rituals.
And I confirmed that to be true because
after my Bible school I started
preaching the Word of God
and praying for people as well.
One evening while I was passing, I met this guy on the floor whilst people were gathered around him.
And then, the guy was saying that he was seeing some sort of demons,
using sticks to pierce his chest and that he was dying.
And so I was moved by the power of
God to pray for this guy.
So I went home, took my anointing oil
and came back and then started praying.
As soon as I started this guy rose
up and started beating me.
He started beating me.
And then the following day, I felt I was not okay.
I started having this feeling of
taking ritual money myself.
So, it continued till one day I met one
of my friend who took me to a ritualist
to take ritual money.
They demanded for five human
fingers and then an embryo.
Which I was not able to get,
so I left and then relocated to
another town with my wife.
Over there everything was destroyed.
My business was destroyed and
this feeling became very strong -
that I need
to take this money
and be free at once and for all.
So I started going out looking for
where I would get it.
So when I came here with my wife to Nigeria,
it became so strong that I told myself:
"Okay, this is the time I need to take it".
So I came and then went around looking for
somewhere to take this money.
I went there with a mind that
anything that they demanded
from me I would be ready to
give out then.
So I went to this ritualist and
told him about my situation,
I told him that I wanted money and he said
that before he could commence anything,
I should bring 10 000 Naira
so that we could continue.
I didn't have the money so I told him I would be back.
When I came home, I came to
SCOAN with my wife and that's when
I encountered the Man of God with that prophecy.
After the prophecy, the thought
of taking this rituals is gone.
During those days, I used to dream, seeing
those short, short demons coming
to me, chasing me with axe.
I saw people coming to steal my money.
I had a whole lot of dreams, this days I
don't have those dreams any longer.
So I give thanks to God for delivering me.
Testimony Time
There is trouble all over the world.
Because even the trouble in the
House of God is so much.
Who is a pastor now? Who is a prophet all over the world?
That is the trouble now.
There is trouble, so we need to pray for the church.
Please rise up, let's pray for the church.
Pray for the church. Ask God to redeem the church.
Redeem the assembly.
Ask God to purge the church.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ we pray.
Ask God to purge the church - overhaul the church.
In Jesus Christs' name we pray.
Remember your pastor in prayer.
Ask God to guide your pastor.
If your pastor needs to be purged,
ask God to purge him.
Purge him, sanctify him.
Make the real church, let the
church of the Acts
of Apostle come down in our day.
In Jesus Christs' name.
So brother, you have seen everything
that happened. So we thank God.
If I was you now and I was
a pastor and was still claiming on,
why can't you just let us pray
and ask God for direction.
Okay, I think this is what we're
going to do now.
So thank you.
We believe you have been inspired
by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today.
And stay up to date for the latest prophecies,
deliverances, sermons and testimonies from The Synagogue Church of all Nations.
Emmanuel TV
Changing Lives, Changing Nations
and Changing The World
TT: Lizz ndungu 10/7/2017
RV: Jacqueline 07/01/18